Minami Mukai

Mountain View, California, United States

mitukaichi@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/minami-itsukaichi

Summary

A senior program manager with 10+ years experience of data analytics, scaled operations and project management in a high-velocity product team. Specialized in understanding complex need, handling complex data and designing product operations with detail-oriented, customer-centric mindset.

Experience

G Program Manager

Google

May 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Manage the global QA operations of Google Ads human review quality, working closely with engineering team to set up the QA program, establish the reliable measurement, build dashboards and conduct data-driven analysis to provide insights to the senior leadership in the engineering team to propose the quality improvement plans.

G Solutions Consultant

Google

Jun 2016 - May 2022 (6 years)

Lead the global product operations to onboard and retain publishers feeding the data to run various Google products. Conducted data analysis and proposed product improvements to the engineering team based on the publisher data quality, customer activity and sales data, which enabled multiple launches to increase the revenue and improve the data quality.

G Solutions Consultant

Google Japan

Apr 2009 - Jun 2016 (7 years 3 months)

Education

Berkeley Extension Berkeley Extension

Full Stack Web Developer 2023 - 2023

The University of Tokyo

Bachelor of Arts, American Literature (United States) 2005 - 2009

Licenses & Certifications

Teaching Certificate in Japan

Skills

Node.js • React.js • JavaScript • Express.js • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • SQL • Operations Management • Project Management • Japanese • Python (Programming Language)